[{"question":"Taroko Gorge (太魯閣), a ______ scenic spot, is located in Hualien.","answer":"well-known","op1":"formal","op2":"warm-hearted","op3":"graceful"},{"question":"The committee went ______ the proposals for a second time.","answer":"over","op1":"away","op2":"under","op3":"on"},{"question":"In my opinion, it’s important not to ______ in this kind of political dispute.","answer":"take sides","op1":"put down","op2":"give off","op3":"tell apart"},{"question":"The current economic recession is threatening the ______ of many people in the country.","answer":"livelihoods","op1":"qualifications","op2":"maturity","op3":"substance"},{"question":"Yu-lin and her brothers gave their parents a big party in ______ of their 50th wedding anniversary.","answer":"honor","op1":"charge","op2":"favor","op3":"care"},{"question":"Due to Typhoon Emerson, the price of vegetables has ______ greatly over the past few days.","answer":"fluctuated","op1":"expanded","op2":"influenced","op3":"adjusted"},{"question":"Don’t be troubled by Amanda’s frequent angry moods. It’s just ______ of her illness.","answer":"a manifestation","op1":"a consistency","op2":"an abundance","op3":"an enforcement"},{"question":"Bruce read two film scripts; he didn’t enjoy one, a comedy, but he did enjoy ______, a thriller.","answer":"the other","op1":"one another","op2":"ano ther","op3":"other"},{"question":"Tourists have left a lot of soda cans and plastic bags in and ______ the park.","answer":"around","op1":"at","op2":"on","op3":"through"},{"question":"When Paul and Ann were children, they ______ visit their cousins in Chicago from time to time.","answer":"would","op1":"were to","op2":"might","op3":"should"},{"question":"______ that something like this would happen to me.","answer":"Never in my wildest dreams did I imagine","op1":"In ever did my wildest dreams imagine in","op2":"I did never imagine in my wildest dreams","op3":"In my wildest dreams did I never imagine"},{"question":"Some of Curt Wilder’s books have been widely read ______ others have remained relatively unknown.","answer":"while","op1":"except","op2":"until","op3":"since"},{"question":"Kuo-hwa, an optimist, is always cheerful, ______ hardships with an eagerness to overcome them.","answer":"facing","op1":"faces","op2":"faced","op3":"toface"},{"question":"To our surprise, Tina was given permission to enter the third grade, although she ______ the previous grade.","answer":"hadn't passed","op1":"doesn't pass","op2":"ought not to pass","op3":"not passing"},{"question":"I hope to do as ______ swimming this summer as I did last year.","answer":"much","op1":"a lot","op2":"possible","op3":"many times"},{"question":"After the police arrive, they will begin to interview the people who ______ in the jewelry store at the time of the robbery.","answer":"were","op1":"have been","op2":"are","op3":"will be"},{"question":"The city government _______ to build a new sports stadium in preparation for the coming Olympics. ","answer":"is planning","op1":"which plans","op2":"is going to plan","op3":"planning"},{"question":"New computer technology has _______ changed the way Hollywood movies are made.","answer":"dramatically","op1":"sincerely","op2":"greedily","op3":"idly"},{"question":"This proposal for a new high speed train _______ because the cost is too high.","answer":"will be rejected","op1":"had been rejected","op2":"has rejected","op3":"rejected"},{"question":"_______ many desirable qualities which make it a commercially very useful metal.","answer":"Aluminum has","op1":"That aluminum has","op2":"Aluminum having","op3":"Aluminum to have"},{"question":"Ms. Chen _______ her position as the new conductor of the National Orchestra only a few weeks before the fall concert season began.","answer":"took up","op1":"bent over","op2":"picked out","op3":"drove down"},{"question":"So far this year four typhoons, two of them very strong, _______ southern Taiwan.","answer":"have struck","op1":"have been struck","op2":"will strike","op3":"were striking"},{"question":"Depending on the _______ he is in, the boss will either thank you for your suggestion or fire you for criticizing his plan.","answer":"mood","op1":"behavior","op2":"emotion","op3":"attitude"},{"question":"If a typist wishes to type rapidly, he _______ develop a rhythmic movement of his fingers. ","answer":"must","op1":"used to","op2":"would","op3":"had to"},{"question":"During the experiment, a constant temperature of 28 degree Celsius was _______ while the amount of sunlight was gradually increased.","answer":"maintained","op1":"performed","op2":"continued","op3":"expanded"},{"question":"Construction of the new highway system _______ completed on time if more workers had been hired.","answer":"would have been","op1":"needs to be","op2":"will be","op3":"should have"},{"question":"Mary is one of my best friends, but sometimes the way she keeps changing her mind _______ on my nerves.","answer":"gets","op1":"getting","op2":"gotten","op3":"toget"},{"question":"Nepal , a small country located between Tibet and India, has _______ of 11.3 million, most of whom are Mongol or Aryan.","answer":"population","op1":"aland","op2":"taxation","op3":"arms"},{"question":"Defensive drivers _______ their driving mirrors frequently so that they know at all times if there are other vehicles or people nearby.","answer":"look in","op1":"check into","op2":"see to","op3":"watch out"},{"question":"_______ newspaper reports, flooding in the area near the river due to the storm has been much more serious than expected.","answer":"According to","op1":"Including some","op2":"For","op3":"As"},{"question":"Flight 305 _______ depart at 3:30 p.m. but was cancelled because of a mechanical problem in one of the engines.","answer":"was supposed to","op1":"ought to","op2":"is assumed to","op3":"might have to"},{"question":"Susan had a terrible day today. First she  _____ up by a strange phone call at four o’clock this morning. ","answer":"was woken","op1":"woke","op2":"wakes","op3":"is awake"},{"question":"What was _____ , when she got home this afternoon, she couldn’t open the door because she had left her keys at her office.","answer":"worse","op1":"harder","op2":"later","op3":"angrier"},{"question":"It seems _____ as people devote more and more time to using the Internet","answer":"that","op1":"to","op2":"where","op3":"yet"},{"question":"Visitors can start their ______ on one lake.","answer":"journey","op1":"flight","op2":"hike","op3":"course"},{"question":"The first Sherlock Holmes story _______ by a doctor named Arthur Conan Doyle in 1886.","answer":"was written","op1":"being written","op2":"wrote","op3":"written"},{"question":"In the four years from 1989 to 1992, the gross national product _______ by an average of over 10% per year.","answer":"fell","op1":"falls","op2":"is falling","op3":"will fall"},{"question":"The original frame, which was made of gold, was soon _______ a marble one before it could be stolen.","answer":"replaced with","op1":"held on","op2":"put in","op3":"moved in"},{"question":"The architect of the new five-star hotel received several awards for her _______ design.","answer":"elegant","op1":"opposite","op2":"admiring","op3":"courteous"},{"question":"Until recently it had been generally accepted that one of the greatest milestones in human history was the _______ of an agricultural lifestyle.","answer":"adoption","op1":"devotion","op2":"excitement","op3":"interest"},{"question":"Only by making fundamental changes will it _______ possible to bring the crisis to a close.","answer":"be","op1":"but also","op2":"maybe","op3":"then"},{"question":"Even though the television networks claim there has been _______ in the number of children watching television, research shows that children are actually watching more than before.","answer":"a decrease","op1":"a growth","op2":"an impact","op3":"a trend"},{"question":"If you wanted to get students excited about the subject, you could take some time to plan some field trips that would really _______.","answer":"turn them on","op1":"fill them out","op2":"bring them up","op3":"make them up"},{"question":"The pilots will stay away from work next week _______ a new agreement with the airline company can be signed.","answer":"unless","op1":"whether","op2":"except","op3":"once"},{"question":"_______ someone oppose abortion for reasons of faith, he may be criticized for imposing his religious beliefs on others.","answer":"Should","op1":"Might","op2":"Could","op3":"Would"},{"question":"Register early if you would like to attend next Tuesday’s _____ on project management. ","answer":"seminar","op1":"reason","op2":"policy","op3":"scene"},{"question":"Paul Brown resigned last Monday from his position as _____ executive of the company. ","answer":"chief","op1":"fine","op2":"front","op3":"large"},{"question":"The financial audit of Soft Peach Software _____ completed on Wednesday by a certified accounting firm. ","answer":"was","op1":"having been","op2":"to be","op3":"were"},{"question":"The organizers of the trip reminded participants to _____ at the steps of the city hall at 2:00 P.M. ","answer":"meet","op1":"combine","op2":"see","op3":"go"},{"question":"_____ is no better season than winter to begin training at Silver’s Fitness Center.","answer":"There","op1":"When","op2":"It","op3":"Asit"},{"question":"The recent worldwide increase in oil prices has led to a _____ demand for electric vehicles.","answer":"greater","op1":"greatest","op2":"greatly","op3":"greatness"},{"question":"Maria Vásquez has a wide range of experience, _____ worked in technical, production, and marketing positions.","answer":"having","op1":"has","op2":"having had","op3":"had"},{"question":"Tickets will not be redeemable for cash or credit at any time, _____ will they be replaced if lost or stolen. ","answer":"nor","op1":"though","op2":"but","op3":"only"},{"question":"There is water on the floor. Be careful, or you will ________ .","answer":"slip","op1":"smiled","op2":"straighten","op3":"spoil"},{"question":"For several years now, we have seen a marked ______ in attendance and exhibitions at the PCB design conferences. ","answer":"increase","op1":"increased","op2":"increasing","op3":"TO increase"},{"question":"The _____ of Peabody Wing will take place over most of 2016 and is broken up into several phases. ","answer":"renovation","op1":"transaction","op2":"profitability","op3":"occupation"},{"question":"There is a nice little gift shop where you can buy _____ for your people back home. ","answer":"souvenirs","op1":"reminders","op2":"processes","op3":"suggestions"},{"question":"Before returning the goods, please inspect all containers to ensure that they are undamaged and _____ placed.","answer":"properly","op1":"approximately","op2":"significantly","op3":"systematically"},{"question":" Although the _____ of installation is very easy, only trained technicians are permitted to  perform the operation. ","answer":"procedure","op1":"alternative","op2":"duration","op3":"statement"},{"question":"Microscopes are used in medical research labs for studying bacteria or ______ that are too small to be visible to the naked eye.","answer":"germs","op1":"indexes","op2":"codes","op3":"agencies"},{"question":"Lisa hopped on her bicycle and ______ as fast as she could through the dark narrow backstreets to get home after working the night shift.","answer":"pedaled","op1":"bounced","op2":"commuted","op3":"tumbled"},{"question":"Rated as one of the top restaurants of the city, this steak house is highly ______ to visitors by the tourism bureau.","answer":"recommended","op1":"outnumbered","op2":"encountered","op3":"speculated"},{"question":"The manager ______ agreed to rent his apartment to me. Even though the agreement was not put in writing, I am sure he will keep his word.","answer":"verbally","op1":"stably","op2":"barely","op3":"massively"},{"question":"For Jerry, practicing yoga three times a week is a relaxing ______ from his tight work schedule.","answer":"diversion","op1":"medication","op2":"nuisance","op3":"fulfillment"},{"question":"Parents could be charged with neglect or abandonment if they leave their young children home alone without adult ______.","answer":"supervision","op1":"intuition","op2":"compassion","op3":"obligation"},{"question":"Walking at a ______ pace for a shorter amount of time burns more calories than walking at a slow pace for a longer period of time","answer":"brisk","op1":"superb","op2":"joyous","op3":"decent"},{"question":"Plants and animals in some deserts must cope with a climate of ______—freezing winters and very hot summers.","answer":"extremes","op1":"forecasts","op2":"atmospheres","op3":"homelands"},{"question":"The success of J.K. Rowling is ______, with her Harry Potter series making her a multi-millionaire in just a few years","answer":"legendary","op1":"confidential","op2":"marginal","op3":"eligible"},{"question":"The high-tech company’s ______ earnings surely made its shareholders happy since they were getting a good return on their investment.","answer":"robust","op1":"solitary","op2":"imperative","op3":"terminal"},{"question":"There are no easy solutions to the _____, not to mention solutions that are agreeable to all parties.","answer":"problem","op1":"aged","op2":"deteriorating","op3":"statue"},{"question":"John is very close to his family. Whenever he feels depressed, he returns to the warm, ______, and comfortable atmosphere of his home.","answer":"secure","op1":"crucial","op2":"sloppy","op3":"cautious"},{"question":"Tom ______ something before he left the room, but I couldn’t figure out exactly what he said.","answer":"mumbled","op1":"perceived","op2":"summoned","op3":"trampled"},{"question":"The content of the book is very much technical and specialized; it is too difficult for a ______ to understand.","answer":"layman","op1":"hacker","op2":"patriot","op3":"tenant"},{"question":"Food shortages are one of the main causes of ______ nutrition among children in developing countries.","answer":"inadequate","op1":"vigorou","op2":"distinctive","op3":"abundant"},{"question":"Good writers do not always write ______; on the contrary, they often express what they really mean in an indirect way","answer":"explicitly","op1":"ironically","op2":"persistently","op3":"selectively"},{"question":"Mr. Jackson is a very ______ writer; people of all ages enjoy his stories.","answer":"popular","op1":"honest","op2":"polite","op3":"easy"},{"question":"Carol sounded happy when we talked on the phone; I could feel joy in her ______.","answer":"voice","op1":"smile","op2":"mail","op3":"eyes"},{"question":"Have you got anything for Joe ______? He'd be happy to get your gift on his birthday.","answer":"yet","op1":"almost","op2":"either","op3":"soon"},{"question":"Susan bought ______ bread in the supermarket, but she did not buy anything to drink.","answer":"some","op1":"any","op2":"many","op3":"one"},{"question":"Playing sports at least three times a week ______ good for your health.","answer":"is","op1":"are","op2":"has rejected","op3":"have"},{"question":"My parents have different hobbies. One enjoys baking; ______ enjoys taking pictures.","answer":"the other","op1":"another","op2":"the next","op3":"the second"},{"question":"My mom told me to take care of ______ in England. She worried that I couldn't eat or sleep well there.","answer":"myself","op1":"me","op2":"her","op3":"herself"},{"question":"The paint on the wall is not as ______ as it was ten years ago. It has changed from white to gray.","answer":"bright","op1":"heavy","op2":"sure","op3":"young"},{"question":"I told you this road went the wrong way, but you just wouldn't listen. Now we have to ______ and take another road.","answer":"turn back","op1":"go head","op2":"move away","op3":"passby"},{"question":"Ken's brothers like to watch tennis, but Ken _______. He is crazy about baseball.","answer":"doesn't","op1":"is","op2":"isn't","op3":"does"},{"question":"Please speak ______ to those children with hearing problems so that they can read your lips more easily and understandbetter.","answer":"slowly","op1":"honestly","op2":"politely","op3":"quietly"},{"question":"My father told me last night ______ we're going to the Food Festival this weekend. My brother and I felt very excited.","answer":"that","op1":"whether","op2":"where","op3":"what"},{"question":"I saw Nora in the teacher's office this morning. Do you know _______ she was there?","answer":"why","op1":"how","op2":"if","op3":"when"},{"question":"I'm really sorry, but the kitchen is very busy. You'll have it _______.","answer":"soon","op1":"once","op2":"aleardy","op3":"early"},{"question":"Sorry, but I didn't hear the question you asked. Could you please ______ it?","answer":"advise","op1":"talk","op2":"answer","op3":"repeat"},{"question":"Jim grew up with many animals at home and knows well how to ______ pets.","answer":"take care of","op1":"wake up","op2":"get away from","op3":"belong"},{"question":"Connie took off her ______. She wanted to feel the grass with her feet.","answer":"shoes and socks","op1":"shirt and pants","op2":"cap and gloves","op3":"sweater and jacket"},{"question":"You can't _______ Tasty Bakery's meat pie! It's so delicious that even some restaurants in town order it.","answer":"miss","op1":"hit","op2":"hit","op3":"cut"},{"question":"I write down everything about work in my pink notebook; ______ it, I'd forget the things I should do.","answer":"without","op1":"outside","op2":"before","op3":"except"},{"question":"I can't believe you ate the ______ piece of pizza and didn't even leave one bite for me.","answer":"last","op1":"least","op2":"less","op3":"most"},{"question":"You're really ______ to go swimming in the lake on a cold winter day. Don't you feel cold?","answer":"crazy","op1":"smart","op2":"sweet","op3":"weak"},{"question":"There is no ______ near the theater, so let's take the bus there.","answer":"parking space","op1":"freshair","op2":"bright light","op3":"great food"},{"question":"I want to go camping in the mountains this afternoon, but a typhoon is coming. I'm not sure ______ the road to the mountains will be closed.","answer":"weather","op1":"how","op2":"what","op3":"why"},{"question":"Joseph was painting the wall when the phone rang. He quickly ______ his brush and ran to answer it.","answer":"put down","op1":"gave up","op2":"handed in","op3":"took away"},{"question":"The boss called from the airport an hour ______, so I guess he will arrive at the office soon.","answer":"ago","op1":"after","op2":"before","op3":"later"}]